ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5744
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- News clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 40: Stix Defies Boycott Committee by Advertising J. P. Stevens Goods: Others Also Refuse Cooperation, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    St. Louis Labor Tribune. July 27, 1978
  - Item 41: Taking the Heat for J. P. Stevens, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Industry Week. October 29, 1979
  - Item 42: The Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Detroit Free Press. March 28, 1978
  - Item 43: The Textile Workers vs. J. P. Stevens: A Boycott in Behalf of Workers' Rights, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Christianity and Crisis. April 4, 1977
  - Item 44: The Voice of the People, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 45: Trouble In The Sheets: The J. P. Stevens Struggle, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Politicks and Other Human Interests. February 28, 1978
  - Item 46: Union Hurting Stevens In Board Room War, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Charlotte Observer. March 22, 1978
  - Item 47: Union Wins Election at J. P. Stevens Plant, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Washington Post. October 6, 1979
  - Item 48: Union Wins Representation at Textile Plant: 2nd Victory in Bitter J. P. Stevens Fight, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 49: Union's Goal Is To Force All Workers Into Unions, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Southern Textile News. March 20, 1978
  - Item 50: Union's Win Tastes Sweet To Ex-Worker, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Charlotte Observer. August 24, 1979
- News clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Appeals Court Issues Angry Opinion: J. P. Stevens Again In Contempt For Flouting U.S. Court Orders, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Press Associates. September 5, 1977
  - Item 2: Boycott J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    UAW Solidarity. September 9, 1977
  - Item 3: Crystal Lee Sutton interview, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Ella May Wiggins Day, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    National Organization for Women (NOW). September 15, 1979
  - Item 5: Ella May Wiggins, Slain In 1929 During Strike, Will Be Honored, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Former Attorney General Griffin Bell's law firm, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Politics Today. September - October 1979
  - Item 7: From the President, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The Inovator. April 1977
  - Item 8: In the Land of Cheap Laborr: Hooded Anachronisms, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The Record. August 14, 1979
  - Item 9: J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Martin L. Levinson. August 30, 1977
  - Item 10: J. P. Stevens Plant Votes for Union, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The Sunday Record. October 7, 1979
  - Item 11: Look For The Union Label, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The Record. September 13, 1979
  - Item 12: Martin President Backs Anti-Union Group, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Henry County Journal. April 28, 1977
  - Item 13: Message Held 'Chilling' For the Union Election, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The Washington Star. August 28, 1979
  - Item 14: NLRB Decision: It Violated Workers' Rights, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The Charlotte Observer. August 27, 1979
  - Item 15: No Happy Ending For the Real-Life Norma Rae, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Detroit Free Press. April 13, 1979
  - Item 16: Norma Rae Opens Shop, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Norma Rae: A Name That the Industry Will Not Soon Forget, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    America's Textiles. April 1979
  - Item 18: Roanoke Rapids "We've Got It All", 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    J. P. Stevens Employees Education Committee. August 5, 1979
  - Item 19: Stevens OKs Talks, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Stevens Plant Votes for Union, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The New York Times. October 7, 1979
  - Item 21: Stormy Days On The Labor Front, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The Washington Star. September 10, 1979
  - Item 22: Union Seeking Vote at Stevens, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The Washington Star. August 16, 1979
  - Item 23: Union Sues J. P. Stevens, Alleging Georgia Conspiracy, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The New York Times. July 19, 1979
  - Item 24: Urges Boycott Support: Inter-Religious Group Assails 'Immoral' Tactics of Stevens, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Press Associates. October 29, 1979
- News clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 5 Years After Union Victory, Battle Goes On at J. P. Stevens, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Washington Post. August 29, 1979
  - Item 2: 7 Bishops Urge Stevens Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Atlanta Journal. June 6, 1977
  - Item 3: 7 Catholic Bishops Urge Textile Firm To Allow Unions, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Indianapolis Star. June 6, 1977
  - Item 4: A Battleground For Industrial Strife, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: A Bintel Brief, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    "A Bundle of Letters" to the Jewish Daily Forward
  - Item 6: A Follow-Up On the J. P. Stevens Dispute, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Origins: NC Documentary Service. March 30, 1978
  - Item 7: A Ga. Town's Covert War Against Unionism, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Philadelphia Inquirer. August 26, 1979
  - Item 8: Base on J. P. Stevens Worker: 'Norma Rae' Rings True In Its Feminist, Pro-Union Message, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Press Associates. April 2, 1979
  - Item 9: Bishops Are Walking On Air, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Hickory Daily Record. March 16, 1978
  - Item 10: Bishops Back Stevens Workers: 7 Catholic Prelates Offer to Mediate, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Charlotte Observer. June 7, 1977
  - Item 11: Bishops Blast Textile Firm, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Catholic Review. March 17, 1978
  - Item 12: Bishops Err On Stevens Union Fight, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Greenville Piedmont. June 14, 1977
  - Item 13: Bishops Offer Again to Mediate In J. P. Stevens Dispute, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    National Catholic Reporter. December 1977
  - Item 14: Bishops Offer To Act As Mediators In Stevens Dispute, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    NC News Service. May 27, 1979
  - Item 15: Bishops Offer To Act As Stevens Mediators, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Catholic Banner. June 16, 1977
  - Item 16: Bishops Offer to Meet With Stevens, Textile Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    NC News Service. December 5, 1977
  - Item 17: Bishops' Position Upsets Stevens Co., 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Church in the U.S.
  - Item 18: Bishops Seek to Mediate Textile Workers Dispute, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Origins NC Documentary Service. June 9, 1977
  - Item 19: Bishops Should Stop Meddling, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Charlotte Observer. June 12, 1977
  - Item 20: Bishops Urge Unionization, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Bishops-Stevens Meet: Talk, No Action, Yet, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    National Catholic Reporter. February 1978
  - Item 22: Boycott of Textile Company Supported at 75 Colleges, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Chronicle of Higher Education. November 6, 1978
  - Item 23: Boycott, Unionization of J. P. Stevens Splits Catholics in North Carolina, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    National Catholic Reporter. October 1977
  - Item 24: Boycotts Called On Stevens and Nestle, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    United Presbyterian. June 1979
  - Item 25: Catalpa Tree Sweet Paradise, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Chapter from Rise Gonna Rise: A Portrait of Southern Textile Workers by Mimi Conway
  - Item 26: Catholic Bishops Attack Stevens 'Anti-Unionism', 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Gastonia Gazette. March 15, 1978
  - Item 27: Catholic Bishops Back Union at J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Knoxville News-Sentinel. June 6, 1977
  - Item 28: Catholic Bishops Criticize 'Anti-Union', 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Hickory Daily Record. March 15, 1978
  - Item 29: Catholic Bishops Offer to Mediate the J. P. Stevens-ACTWU Controversy, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    News Release.
  - Item 30: Clothing Union Names J. P. Stevens, Others In Conspiracy Suit, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    July 19.
  - Item 31: Collective Bargaining, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Winston-Salem Sentinel. December 10, 1977
  - Item 32: Collective Bargaining Rights of Teachers in Church-Related Schools, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    NC Features. April 9, 1979
  - Item 33: Endorsement of the United Presbyterian Church, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Bill Somplatsky-Jarman. June 5, 1979
  - Item 34: Fair Measure, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Reprint from Southern Exposure. Spring 1979
  - Item 35: From Cotton Mill To Executive Suite, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Washington Star. July 27, 1979
  - Item 36: Human Billboards vs. J. P. Stevens, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Soho Weekly News. October 11-17, 1979
  - Item 37: Illegal Moves Keep Unions Out of Town, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Macon Telegraph. July 24, 1979
  - Item 38: Into the Ring Jumps Another Intruder, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    June 1977.
  - Item 39: J. P. Stevens Boycott Goes Beyond Publicity, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Daily Iowan. June 11, 1979
  - Item 40: J. P. Stevens Company Draws Ire Of Bishops, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Lexington Dispatch. March 16, 1978
  - Item 41: J. P. Stevens Disappointed Over Action, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Fayetteville Observer. March 16, 1978
  - Item 42: J. P. Stevens To Lay Off About 300, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Charlotte Observer. August 23, 1978
  - Item 43: J. P. Stevens Upheld by N.L.R.B. In Dispute on Employee's Ouster, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    UPI; Patrcik J. Sullivan. July 2, 1979
  - Item 44: J. P. Stevens, Union and Bishops Meet, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The North Carolina Catholic. December 18, 1977
  - Item 45: Labor Case Review Asked, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Newsday. August 8, 1979
  - Item 46: Like a Sieve, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Federal Times. July 2, 1979
  - Item 47: Ministers Support Textile Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Harvey Harris.
  - Item 48: Msgr. Geogre Higgins' advice and support, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 49: NLRB Orders New Talks: Bad Faith Bargaining Charge Upheld Against J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Press Associates. December 25, 1978
  - Item 50: No Violence' in Stevens Controversy, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Criterion. April 21, 1978
  - Item 51: Pro-Labor Positions Cited: Leaders From Six National Union Form Carter Reelection Committee, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Press Associates. August 6, 1979
  - Item 52: Rock Hill Printing and Finishing Plant to Cut 150 Jobs, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    June 27.
  - Item 53: Second Thoughts, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Nation, Carey McWillliams. September 8, 1979
  - Item 54: Seven Catholic Bishops in South Urge J. P. Stevens to Allow Unions, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 55: Sleeping With Dinah Could Be Finah, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Village Voice. December 4, 1978
  - Item 56: Southern Textile Workers to Seek 15 Percent Wage Increases in '79, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 57: Statement of Facts, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 58: Stevens Boycott, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    National Catholic Register. July 8, 1979
  - Item 59: Stevens Cited Again for Unfair Practices, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Greenville- Piedmont News. April 20, 1979
  - Item 60: Stevens Determined to Comply With Labor Law, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    J. p. Stevens Corporate Newsletter. May 1979
  - Item 61: Stevens Suit Out; Judge Hits Labor Record, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The News and Observer. August 7, 1979
  - Item 62: Stevens to Bishops: Would Welcome More ACTW Talks, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 63: Strike At Sunnyland Shows Its Bitter Side, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Atlanta Constitution. March 7, 1979
  - Item 64: Support Justice for Textile Workers, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Corporate Campaign Press Alert. October 11, 1979
  - Item 65: Textile Union Protesters Invade Bloomingdale's, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Record. July 20, 1979
  - Item 66: The Churches' Stake, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Sojourners. April 1979
  - Item 67: The Church's Role in Unionizing Southern Mills, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 68: The J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Chronicle of Higher Education. December 11, 1978
  - Item 69: The South: Last Bastion of the Open Shop, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Politics Today. March - April 1979
  - Item 70: The Trouble In Milledgeville: Town vs. Union, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Daily News Record. July 23, 1979
  - Item 71: Three Lowenstein Cotton Mills to Curtail Operations Through Labor Day, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 72: Union Affiliation, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Washington Star.October 2, 1979
  - Item 73: Union Complaint Against J. P. Stevens Dropped, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    July 18.
  - Item 74: Union Film Falters In Roanoke Rapids, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The News and Observer. June 15, 1979
  - Item 75: Union Membership, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Gastonia Gazette. June 13, 1977
  - Item 76: Union Responds To Bishops, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The North Carolina Catholic. April 2, 1978
  - Item 77: Union Votes Up In Region, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 78: United Presbyterians Vote to Back Boycott Of the J. P. Stevens Co., 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The New York Times. May 30, 1979
  - Item 79: United Way Comes Under Increasing Fire in 'Charity War', 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Washington Post. November 23, 1979
  - Item 80: URW Supporters Ordered Rehired At Massachusetts Plant, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Press Associates. February 19, 1979
  - Item 81: When Churchmen Speak, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    the Shelby Daily Star. June 1977
  - Item 82: Bishops Urge Stevens 'Neutrality', 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Criterion. March 1978
  - Item 83: He Hopes to Put the Heat on Business, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
    The Birmingham News. December 1, 1978
  - Item 84: Worker's Arm is Reimplanted, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 5)
- News clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: "Jobholders" Lash Out At Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: "Jobholders" Meeting Likened to Revival, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Greenville Piedmont. March 7, 1978
  - Item 3: "Norma Rae" Different Kind of Labor Film, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Journal- News. November 24, 1978
  - Item 4: 1,500 Pickets Assail Union-Busting Textile Baron, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The News World. October 12, 1979
  - Item 5: A Ga. Town's Covert War Against Unionism, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Philadelphia Inquirer. August 27, 1979
  - Item 6: A Reply On The Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Holyoke Daily Transcript. July 14, 1978
  - Item 7: ACTWU Preparing For Fifth Anniversary, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. August 23, 1979
  - Item 8: Appeals Court Denounces Acts by J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Wall Street Journal. September 1, 1977
  - Item 9: Being Against Labor Unions in the South is No Crime, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Jacksonville News. January 16, 1978
  - Item 10: Bishop Defends Stance On J. P. Stevens Labor Dispute, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Winston-Salem Sentinel. July 6, 1977
  - Item 11: Blacklist Against Milledgeville Union Revealed, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Saturday Telegraph and News. June 30, 1979
  - Item 12: Carter Says U.S. Can't Cut Off J. P. Stevens; Riegle Disagrees, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Detroit Labor News. August 2, 1979
  - Item 13: Consider the Consequences, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    News Free Press. July 8, 1978
  - Item 14: For Stevens Employes, a Union Rally, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Foreign Aid Pledged in Textile Fight, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Washington Post. September 3, 1977
  - Item 16: Grievances Presented HRC In Session, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Roanoke Rapids Sunday Herald. October 21, 1979
  - Item 17: Group Defends Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: J. P. Stevens and Co. vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    National Labor Relations Board, Region 11. March 11, 1977
  - Item 19: J. P. Stevens Labor Case Isn't Closed Yet, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Danbury News-Times. July 10, 1978
  - Item 20: J. P. Stevens On The Spot, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Rushton Daily Leader. June 30, 1978
  - Item 21: J. P. Stevens Press Conference, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    International Textile and Garment and Leather Workers' Federation. July 5, 1979
  - Item 22: Judge Refuses To Transfer Stevens Case, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. April 7, 1978
  - Item 23: Justice! Hogwash, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 24: Lawsuit Filed by JPS Employes to Compel NLRB to Process Union Election Petition, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The News and Observer. December 1, 1978
  - Item 25: Macy's Ignores Boycott On Stevens Products, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The New Haven Register. September 18, 1979
  - Item 26: NLRB Bargaining Order Hits Stevens Lawlessness, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    AFL- CIO News. September 1, 1979
  - Item 27: NLRB Says Stevens Guilty, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The News and Observer. December 15, 1978
  - Item 28: Religious Leaders Oppose Company, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    New Wilmington Globe. June 29, 1978
  - Item 29: Roanoke Rapids Workers Achieve Gains Despite Absence of Contract, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 30: Stevens Board Chairman Criticizes Union, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Greenville News. March 8, 1978
  - Item 31: Stevens Boycott Gets Foreign Assist, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 32: Stevens Challenges Union: Risk Elections At All Plants, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Daily News Record. March 8, 1978
  - Item 33: Stevens Counters Union Charges, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Trib. March 8, 1978
  - Item 34: Stevens Denies Any Boycott Impact, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Washington Post. March 8, 1978
  - Item 35: Stevens Head Leaving Bank Under Pressure, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The New York Times. March 8, 1978
  - Item 36: Stevens Management Endorsed, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 37: Stevens Manager Denies He Spied on Union, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Macon Telegraph. July 25, 1979
  - Item 38: Stevens Meeting Marked By Turmoil, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 39: Stevens Meeting To Draw National Attention, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Greenville News and Piedmont. March 5, 1978
  - Item 40: Stevens Must Reimburse Union Wallace Plant Organizing Expenses, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The News and Observer. August 23, 1979
  - Item 41: Stevens' Net Fell 7% in Fiscal 1st Period; Annual Meeting Less Hostile Than in '77, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Wall Street Journal. March 8, 1978
  - Item 42: Stevens Officials Are Not Expecting Any Demonstrations, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 43: Stevens Story 'No Surprise', 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Rochester Courier- Journal. July 5, 1978
  - Item 44: Stevens Unions: Deliverance or Devils, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Unon recorder. June 29, 1978
  - Item 45: Stevens Wins in Showdown With Minority Holders, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Washington Star. March 8, 1978
  - Item 46: Still No Contract: Stevens Workers In Roanoke Rapids Rally On Fifth Anniversary of Vote, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Press Associates. September 3, 1979
  - Item 47: Substitutes Motion for Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Hartford Courant. June 29, 1978
  - Item 48: The Battle To Unionize The South, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Baltimore Sun.
  - Item 49: The Union Versus the Mill, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Globe.
  - Item 50: Town Officials Admit Illegal Spying to Thwart Union Organizers, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Washington Post. August 8, 1979
  - Item 51: U.S. Court Denounces Stevens and Rules It In Comtempt 2d Time, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The New York Times. September 1, 1977
  - Item 52: Union Members 'Greet' Stevens Stockholders, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 53: Union Official Vows To Keep Fighting Stevens, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Greenville News and Greenville Piedmont. September 15, 1979
  - Item 54: Unions Rally Against Stevens, Bank, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 55: US Court Lowers Boom On Stevens' Labor Policy, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Daily News Record. September 1, 1977
  - Item 56: Was There a Ring Around a Union's Collar?, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    The Washington Star. September 4, 1979
  - Item 57: What Is The Real J. P. Stevens Issue, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 58: Workers Spied On, Mayor Tells Court, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Atlanta Journal. July 17, 1979
  - Item 59: Helms Says JPS is Propaganda Victim, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 60: Stevens Employees Seek New Vote, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 61: Mayor Backs Textile Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 63: Stevens to Appeal Latest NLRB Ruling, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. Ausgust 23, 1979
- J. P. Stevens and Co. "Straightening Things Out", 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Unionization of the Textile Industry: A Cas Study of J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Earnings Gap in North Carolina, 1975; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 8)
- News clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 3 Big Textile Firms Are Boosting Wages, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: 6 Killed, 30 Injured in Honea Path Clash, 1934; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Greenville Piedmont. June 7, 1978